http://www.point101.com/legal_privacy

Products
For help choosing a product, see our full product guide.
Legal
Please ensure you understand and agree to the following before using this web site
Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy | Disclaimer | Copyright | Company Details
Terms and Conditions of website usage
Welcome to our website. If you continue to browse and use this website you are agreeing to comply with and be
bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our
privacy policy govern Point101’s relationship with you in relation to
this website.
The term “Point101” or
“us” or “we” refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is Unit 64a, Regent Studios, 8 Andrews Road, London, E8 4QN. The term “you” refers to the user or viewer of our website.
The use of this website is
subject to the following terms of use:
The
content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use
only. It is subject to change without notice.
Neither
we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy,
timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and
materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You
acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or
errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors
to the fullest extent permitted by law.
Your
use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own
risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to
ensure that any products, services or information available through this
website meet your specific requirements.
This
website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material
includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and
graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the
copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.
All
trademarks reproduced in this website, which are not the property of, or
licensed to the operator, are acknowledged on the website.
Unauthorised
use of this website may give to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal
offence.
From
time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links
are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not
signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the
content of the linked website(s).
You
may not create a link to this website from another website or document without
Point101’s prior written consent.
Your
use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is
subject to the laws of England and Wales.
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Point101 uses and
protects any information that you give Point101 when you use this website.
Point101 is committed to ensuring that your
privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which
you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it
will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Point101 may change this policy from time to time
by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure
that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 01/01/07.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact
information including email address
demographic information such as post code, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular
for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We
may use the information to improve our products and services.
We
may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or
other information which we think you may find interesting using the email
address which you have provided.
From
time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market
research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
We
may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that
your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or
disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial
procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which
asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the
file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when
you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you
as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs,
likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your
preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to
identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page
traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We
only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data
is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide
you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find
useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your
computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share
with us.
You can choose to accept or
decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can
usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may
prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to
enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have
used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any
control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the
protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting
such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should
exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in
question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the
collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever
you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can
click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody
for direct marketing purposes
if
you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing
purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at marketing@point101.com
We will not sell, distribute or
lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission
or are required by law. We may use your personal information to send you
promotional information about third parties which we think you may find
interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of
personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act
1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information
held on you please write to Yupz.com Limited t/a Point101, Unit 64a, Regent Studios, 8 Andrews Road, London, E8 4QN
If you believe that any
information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to
or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct
any information found to be incorrect.
Website Disclaimer
The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by Point101 and whilst we endeavour to keep the information up-to-date and correct, we make no
representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the
completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect
to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics
contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such
information is therefore strictly at your own risk.
In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage
including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any
loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of
or in connection with the use of this website.
Through this website you are able to link to other websites
which are not under the control of Point101. We have no control over
the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links
does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed
within them.
Every effort is made to keep the website up and running
smoothly. However, Point101 takes no responsibility for and will not
be liable for the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues
beyond our control.
Copyright Notice
This website and its content is copyright of Yupz.com Limited © 2020. All rights reserved.
Any redistribution or reproduction of part or all of the contents in any form is prohibited other than the following:
you may print or download to a local hard disk extracts for your personal and non-commercial use only
you may copy the content to individual third parties for their personal use, but only if you acknowledge the website as the source of the material
You may not, except with our express written permission, distribute or commercially exploit the content. Nor may you transmit it or store it in any other website or other form of electronic retrieval system.
Company Registration Details:
Registered in England
Yupz.com Ltd t/a Point101. Company Number 4082575.
Registered Address on Companies House: Unit 64a Regent Studios, 8 Andrews Road, London E8 4QN
